For National, the premium has
seen an increase of around 18%.
In two minimas, the premium is increasing by around 19%.
This is an update for general insurance companies.
In Standard Health Insurance, the MAP premium has seen an increase of up to 23%
and in two minimas, the
free premium is up 28%. Let's
start with ICC Lombard, where
we can see that the MAP premium has seen an
increase of around 21%.
In two minimas, the increase is around 18%.
However, the market share has decreased by 10-20 points.
In New India Insurance, the premium has seen a 10% increase in the last month. This
premium has seen an increase of only 10% in the last two minimas and
they have made a significant loss in the market share of around 1.5%.
New India Insurance is losing,
whereas if you pay attention to Star Health, a
16% increase has been seen in the free premium in the last month.
In the last two minimas, there has been a
20% increase
in the premium and their mother  The chair is rising very high.
0.3%, so these are in fact data points that have been extracted by
insurance companies.